Big dreams and big thrills
Flying high, imagine the absurd
Flying high coba bayangkan hal yang tak masuk akal
Flying high とんでもない想像をしてみて
Flying high 터무니없는 상상해봐
Flying high Imagina lo absurdo
ลองจินตนาการแบบไร้เหตุผล
Flying high 天马行空地想象一下
Flying high hãy thử tưởng tượng những điều phi lý đi
A star rushing over in front of your eyes
Bintang yang tiba-tiba muncul di depan matamu
君の目の前に飛びかかってきている星
네 눈앞에 달려들고 있는 별
Estrellas que se arrojan en frente de ti
ดวงดาวที่เด่นอยู่ตรงหน้า
将扑向你眼前的星星
Một ngôi sao rơi vào ánh mắt bạn
Grab it and set it on fire
Tangkap dan coba bakar dia
釣り上げて燃やしてみて
낚아 채 불을 태워 봐
Atrápalas y enciende el fuego
ตกมันมาและจุดไฟให้มัน
拽过来点燃火焰
Bắt lấy và thiêu đốt đi
Can you believe it's only the beginning?
Apa kau bisa percaya itu adalah titik awal?
始まりってことを君は信じられるの？
시작이라는 걸 넌 믿을 수 있겠니?
¿Puedes creer que es el comienzo?
เชื่อไหมว่านี่เป็นเพียงจุดเริ่มต้น
你相信所谓的开始吗
Bạn có tin đây mới chỉ là sự khởi đầu không?
I think I finally know what love is
Sepertinya baru sekarang aku bisa memahami cinta
やっと愛が分かりそう
이제야 사랑을 알 것 같아
Es ahora que creo comprender el amor
ฉันน่าจะเพิ่งรู้จักความรักก็ตอนนี้
现在才明白爱是什么
Giờ đây tôi mới biết thế nào là yêu
Ready or not we're going, trust me
Ready or not kita mulai, percayalah padaku
Ready or not 行くのさ　僕を信じて
Ready or not 가는 거야 나를 믿어
Ready or not Vamos, confía en mí
Ready or not เชื่อฉันนะ
Ready or not 就是要走 相信我
Ready or not đi thôi nào, hãy tin mình
Soldiers knocking doors down yelling out
Forget about the war-like times, my heart shouts
Hempaskan ke belakang waktu-waktu yang bagai perang, dada pun berteriak
戦争　戦争のような時間をすべて後まわしにして　胸が叫ぶよ
전쟁 전쟁 같던 시간들은 모두 뒤로 보내 가슴이 소리치네
Guerras momentos que parecían guerras mándalas para atrás grita el corazón
ใจมันกรีดร้อง ให้ปล่อยช่วงเวลาที่เป็นดั่งสงครามไว้ข้างหลัง
战争般的时间都抛在脑后 内心呼喊
Bỏ lại hết quãng thời gian như một cuộc chiến, trái tim thét gào
Run and fly
Larilah, terbanglah
走っていって　飛んでみて
달려가 날아 봐
Corre y vuela
วิ่งแล้วโบยบินไป
跑起来 飞起来吧
Hãy thử chạy và bay đi nào
If you're rocking with me oh oh
Here we go here we go satellite radio
Let my future know
Sampaikan pada masa depanku
僕の未来に伝えてくれ
내 미래에 전해 줘
Transmítelo a mi futuro
บอกอนาคตของฉันที
转告我的未来
Hãy chuyển lời đến tương lai của tôi
Over the whole world and KWANGYA
Di seluruh dunia dan KWANGYA
世界中とあのKWANGYAの上に
온 세상과 저 광야 위로
A todo el mundo y hacia KWANGYA
ทั่วโลกและ KWANGYA
向着全世界和整个KWANGYA
Với toàn thế giới và cả KWANGYA rằng
For me to say I loved without regrets
Katakan aku telah mencintai tanpa rasa sesal
後悔なく愛したと言うよ
후회 없이 사랑했다고 말하게
Diré que he amado sin arrepentirme
ว่าฉันได้รักโดยไม่มีอะไรต้องเสียใจ
毫不后悔地说出我爱你
Tôi đã yêu mà không chút hối tiếc
I've been waiting for you, welcome
Aku telah menunggu, cepatlah kemari
待っていたよ　ようこそ
기다렸어 어서 와
Te esperé bienvenido
ฉันรออยู่ รีบมาเลย
等待着你 快来吧
Mình đã luôn chờ đợi bạn, chào mừng bạn
Wherever it may be, we’re coming together
Di manapun we’re coming together
どこにでも we’re coming together
어디든 we’re coming together
we’re coming together we’re coming together
ไม่ว่าที่ไหน we’re coming together
不论哪里 we’re coming together
Bất kỳ nơi đâu we’re coming together
Don't worry about anything
Tak perlu khawatir tentang apa pun
何も心配するな
아무 걱정 하지 마
No te preocupes de nada
ก็อย่าได้กังวลสิ่งใด
什么都不用担心
Đừng lo lắng gì cả
It'll be alright, Hello Future
Pasti akan berhasil, Hello Future
うまくいくから Hello Future
잘 될 거야 Hello Future
Todo saldrá bien Hello Future
มันจะไม่เป็นไร Hello Future
一切都会好的 Hello Future
Mọi chuyện sẽ ổn thôi Hello Future
Because I met you, we shine brighter together yeah yeah
Bertemu denganmu, bersama menjadi lebih bersinar yeah yeah
君に出会って共にさらに輝く yeah yeah
너를 만나 같이 더 빛나 yeah yeah
Junto a ti brillo más yeah yeah
ฉันได้พบเธอ แล้วเราเจิดจรัสไปด้วยกัน yeah yeah
遇见你 一起更加闪耀 yeah yeah
Gặp được bạn, chúng ta cùng tỏa sáng hơn nữa yeah yeah
Ey we’re on the way up we’re on the way up
Let's build only with beautiful times yeah yeah yeah
Mari kita buat kenangan yang indah saja yeah yeah yeah
美しい時間だけを築こう yeah yeah yeah
아름다운 시간만 쌓자 yeah yeah yeah
Solo atesoremos los bellos momentos yeah yeah yeah
สร้างแต่ช่วงเวลาที่สวยงามกัน yeah yeah yeah
只积累美好的时间 yeah yeah yeah
Hãy cùng vun đắp bằng những khoảnh khắc tươi đẹp yeah yeah yeah
We’re going way up we’re going
On our way up Hello Future
Ey I got to meet your future self
Ey dipertemukan dengan dirimu di masa depan
Ey 未来の君に遭遇することになった
Ey 미래의 너를 조우하게 됐어
Ey Me encontré con el futuro tú
Ey ฉันบังเอิญพบเธอในอนาคต
Ey 遇见未来的你
Ey Mình đã gặp được bạn ở tương lai đó
When we put our hands together above the boundary, we are so alike
Jika kita satukan tangan di atas batas, kita sangat mirip
境界の上で手を合わせると　僕たちはあまりにも似ている
경계 위로 손을 맞대면 우린 너무 닮아 있어
Si arriba del límite nos tocamos las manos, tú y yo nos parecemos tanto
เมื่อแตะมือบนขอบเส้น เราก็เหมือนกัน
在边界之上手碰手 我们如此相像
Tay trong tay cùng vượt qua ranh giới, chúng ta thật giống nhau
What more will we find or will we smile in the end
Entah apa lagi yang akan dicari, atau akan berakhir dengan tawa
何をもっと探せるようになるだろうか　最後には笑えるのだろうか
뭘 더 찾게 될지 결국 웃게 될지
Tal vez encontraremos algo más o al final sonreiremos
ไม่ว่าเธอจะพบอะไร หรือจะได้หัวเราะ
还会找到什么 最终是否会笑
Chẳng biết có tìm thêm được gì hay cuối cùng chúng ta lại mỉm cười
Call it a fate from now on
Sebut saja takdir mulai sekarang
今からは運命だという
지금부턴 운명이라고 해
Desde ahora digamos que es el destino
ต่อจากนี้ไป จงเรียกมันว่าโชคชะตา
从现在起归于命运
Từ bây giờ hãy gọi đó là định mệnh
Fire fire like a small flower that has survived in the thick smoke
Fire fire bagai bunga kecil yang selamat di tengah pekatnya asap
Fire fire もやもやの煙の中で生き残った背の低い花のように
Fire fire 자욱한 연기 속에 살아남은 키 작은 꽃처럼
Como una pequeña flor que sobrevivió en el denso humo
Fire fire ดั่งดอกไม้เล็กๆ ที่อยู่ในควันหนาทึบ
Fire fire 就像在滚滚浓烟中活下来的小花一样
Fire Fire Như bông hoa nhỏ sống sót giữa làn khói dày đặc
I'm loving you in the same time
Mencintaimu di waktu yang sama
同じ時間の中で　君を愛している
같은 시간 속에 너를 사랑하고 있어
En el mismo timpo te estoy amando
ฉันรักเธอในห้วงเวลาเดียวกัน
同一时间我也在爱着你
Mình yêu bạn cũng trong khoảng thời gian như vậy đấy
Here we go here we go, spread your wings
Here we go here we go bentangkan sayap
Here we go here we go 羽を広げて
Here we go here we go 날개를 펼치고
Here we go here we go Con las alas abiertas
Here we go here we go กางปีกออก
Here we go here we go 展开翅膀
Here we go here we go dang rộng đôi cánh
Even if it gets snapped and get hurt again
Meski patah dan terluka lagi
また折れて怪我しても
또 꺾이고 다쳐도
Aunque me quiebren y me lastime de nuevo
ต่อให้มันหักแล้วเจ็บอีก
就算再次折断受伤
Dù thất vọng, dù tổn thương lần nữa
You're stronger than anyone
Kau lebih kuat dari siapapun
誰より強い君じゃないか
누구보다 강한 너잖아
Tú eres más fuerte que ningún otro
แต่เธอนั้นแข็งแกร่งกว่าใครๆ
你不是比任何人都强大嘛
Bạn mạnh mẽ hơn bất kì ai mà
I'll still love you even in the future and beyond
Aku yang akan mencintai dirimu di masa depan dan seterusnya
未来の未来にも君を愛する僕ということ
미래의 미래에도 널 사랑할 나란 걸
Yo seré quien te ame hasta en el futuro del futuro
ในอนาคตต่อไป ฉันก็จะเป็นคนที่รักเธอ
在未来的未来也会爱你的我
Mình vẫn sẽ yêu bạn trong tương lai và cả mai sau nữa
I've been waiting for you, welcome
Aku telah menunggu, cepatlah kemari
待っていたよ　ようこそ
기다렸어 어서 와
Te esperé bienvenido
ฉันรออยู่ รีบมาเลย
等待着你 快来吧
Mình đã luôn chờ đợi bạn, chào mừng bạn
Wherever it may be, we’re coming together
Di manapun we’re coming together
どこにでも we’re coming together
어디든 we’re coming together
Donde sea we’re coming together
ไม่ว่าที่ไหน we’re coming together
不论哪里 we’re coming together
Bất kỳ nơi đâu we’re coming together
Don't worry about anything
Tak perlu khawatir tentang apa pun
何も心配するな
아무 걱정 하지 마
No te preocupes de nada
ก็อย่าได้กังวลสิ่งใด
什么都不用担心
Đừng lo lắng gì cả
It'll be alright, Hello Future
Pasti akan berhasil, Hello Future
うまくいくから Hello Future
잘 될 거야 Hello Future
Todo saldrá bien Hello Future
มันจะไม่เป็นไร Hello Future
一切都会好的 Hello Future
Mọi chuyện sẽ ổn thôi Hello Future
Because I met you, we shine brighter together yeah yeah
Bertemu denganmu, bersama menjadi lebih bersinar yeah yeah
君に出会って共にさらに輝く yeah yeah
너를 만나 같이 더 빛나 yeah yeah
Junto a ti brillo más yeah yeah
ฉันได้พบเธอ แล้วเราเจิดจรัสไปด้วยกัน yeah yeah
遇见你 一起更加闪耀 yeah yeah
Gặp được bạn, chúng ta cùng tỏa sáng hơn nữa yeah yeah
Ey we’re on the way up we’re on the way up
Ey เรากำลังเดินทางไป เรากำลังเดินทางไป
Let's build only with beautiful times yeah
Mari kita buat kenangan yang indah saja yeah
美しい時間だけを築こう yeah
아름다운 시간만 쌓자 yeah
Solo atesoremos los bellos momentos yeah
สร้างแต่ช่วงเวลาที่สวยงามกัน yeah
只积累美好的时间 yeah
Hãy cùng vun đắp bằng những khoảnh khắc tươi đẹp yeah
We’re going way up we’re going
Ey I’m tryna’ center me hey where your center be?
Will I be able to keep walking unwavering
Tidak tahu apakah akan bisa berjalan dengan teguh
揺れずに歩いていけるんだろうか
흔들리지 않게 걸어 나아갈 수 있을지
Hacia adelante caminando sin temblar podré me pregunto
จะสามารถก้าวไปโดยไม่หวั่นไหวหรือเปล่า
能否毫不动摇地走下去
Liệu tôi có thể bước tiếp mà không hề nao núng
Too many cynical Entropy that went backwards
Too many cynical Entropy berjalan terbalik
Too many cynical 逆に行った Entropy
Too many cynical 거꾸로 갔던 Entropy
Too many cynical Al revés fue Entropy
Too many cynical Entropy ที่เคยถอยหลังกลับ
Too many cynical 逆行的Entropy
Too many cynical, sự đảo ngược hỗn loạn Entropy
I wonder where you will be waiting
Tak tahu harus di mana menunggumu
そのどこかで君は待っているんだろう
그 어디쯤 너 기다리고 있을지
Por ahí me estarás esperando
เธอจะรออยู่ที่ไหน
正在何处等着你
Liệu bạn có đang chờ đợi tôi ở một nơi nào đó
It's not far Open your eyes
Tak akan jauh, bukalah matamu
遠くない　目を開けてみて
멀지 않아 눈을 떠 봐
No queda lejos abre los ojos
อีกไม่ไกลหรอก ลืมตาสิ
并不遥远 睁眼看看
Không còn xa đâu, hãy mở mắt ra
Everything I wanted is you, we're on our way up
Hanya kaulah yang ku inginkan we’re on our way up
僕が欲しがる全ては君だけだと we’re on our way up
내가 원한 모든 건 너뿐이라고 we're on our way up
Todo lo que deseaba era solamente tú we're on our way up
ทั้งหมดที่ฉันต้องการคือเธอ we're on our way up
我想要的只有你而已 we’re on our way up
Tất cả những gì mình mong muốn, chỉ có bạn mà thôi we’re on our way up
In the burnt ashes with tender warmth, ready to clap back
Terbakar, dalam sisa abu yang hangat, ready to clap back
焼けてしまったまま　弱い温もりの残った灰の中に ready to clap back
타 버린 채 여린 온기의 남은 잿더미 속에 ready to clap back
Quemado en el calor delicado en las cenizas que quedaron ready to clap back
ในเถ้าที่แผดเผายังเหลือความอบอุ่น ready to clap back
燃烧殆尽 在留有余温的灰烬中 ready to clap back
Hơi ấm dịu dàng sót lại trong đống tro tàn bị thiêu rụi, ready to clap back
Peace isn't so far away, I only wished and wanted for the painful time to be short
Peace tidak begitu jauh, lagi-lagi berharap waktu yang menyakitkan akan singkat
あまり遠くない peace 辛い時間がすぐ終わるようにと願ってまた願った
그리 멀지 않은 peace 아픈 시간이 다만 짧기를 바라고 또 원했지
No queda tan lejos peace Que las horas de dolor solamente sean cortas esperé y deseé
คำว่า peace อยู่ไม่ไกล และปรารถนาให้เวลาอันเจ็บปวดนั้นสั้นลง
并不遥远的peace 只希望痛苦的时间短暂一些
Bình yên không còn quá xa vời peace tôi chỉ mong khoảng thời gian đau khổ sẽ ngắn lại
Who you gon’ believe?
I've been waiting for you, welcome
Aku telah menunggu, cepatlah kemari
待っていたよ　ようこそ
기다렸어 어서 와
Te esperé bienvenido
ฉันรออยู่ รีบมาเลย
等待着你 快来吧
Mình đã luôn chờ đợi bạn, chào mừng bạn
Wherever it may be, we’re coming together
Di manapun we’re coming together
どこにでも we’re coming together
어디든 we’re coming together
Donde sea we’re coming together
ไม่ว่าที่ไหน we’re coming together
不论哪里 we’re coming together
Bất kỳ nơi đâu we’re coming together
Don't worry about anything
Tak perlu khawatir tentang apa pun
何も心配するな
아무 걱정 하지 마
No te preocupes de nada
ก็อย่าได้กังวลสิ่งใด
什么都不用担心
Đừng lo lắng gì cả
It'll be alright, Hello Future
Pasti akan berhasil, Hello Future
うまくいくから Hello Future
잘 될 거야 Hello Future
Todo saldrá bien Hello Future
มันจะไม่เป็นไร Hello Future
一切都会好的 Hello Future
Mọi chuyện sẽ ổn thôi Hello future
Because I met you, we shine brighter together yeah yeah
Bertemu denganmu, bersama menjadi lebih bersinar yeah yeah
君に出会って共にさらに輝く yeah yeah
너를 만나 같이 더 빛나 yeah yeah
Junto a ti brillo más yeah yeah
ฉันได้พบเธอ แล้วเราเจิดจรัสไปด้วยกัน yeah yeah
遇见你 一起更加闪耀 yeah yeah
Gặp được bạn, chúng ta cùng tỏa sáng hơn nữa yeah yeah
Ey we’re on the way up we’re on the way up
Let's build only with beautiful times yeah
Mari kita buat kenangan yang indah saja yeah
美しい時間だけを築こう yeah
아름다운 시간만 쌓자 yeah
Solo atesoremos los bellos momentos yeah
สร้างแต่ช่วงเวลาที่สวยงามกัน yeah
只积累美好的时间 yeah
Hãy cùng vun đắp bằng những khoảnh khắc tươi đẹp yeah
We’re going way up we’re going
We’re going way up
Stay by my side
Tetaplah berada di sampingku
そばに一緒にいてほしい
곁에 함께 있어줘
Quédate a mi lado
อยู่ข้างๆ ฉันนะ
陪在我身边吧
Hãy ở bên cạnh tôi
Only you are my future
Masa depanku hanyalah dirimu
ただ君だけが僕の未来だということ
오직 너만이 내 미래라는 걸
Solo tú eres mi futuro
มีเพียงเธอเท่านั้นที่เป็นอนาคตของฉัน
只有你是我的未来
Bạn chính là tương lai của tôi
Just keep looking to the stars
I've been waiting for you
Aku telah menunggu
君を待っていた
널 기다렸어
Te estuve esperando
ฉันรอเธออยู่
等待着你
Tôi đã luôn chờ đợi bạn
Hello Future